<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>io.github.joyrider3774.waternet_playdate</id>
  
  <name>Waternet</name>
  <summary>Waternet is a multiplatform puzzle game written for old consoles and handhelds.</summary>
  
  <metadata_license>MIT</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MIT</project_license>
  
  <supports>
    <control>pointing</control>
    <control>keyboard</control>
    <control>gamepad</control>
  </supports>
  
  <description>
    <p>
      The game features 3 Game modes (Rotate, Slide, RoSlid), 5 Difficulties per game mode (very easy, easy, normal, hard, very hard), 25 Levels per difficulty, Unlimited random levels mode per game mode
    </p>
    <p>
      The aim of the game, in any game mode is always to connect all pipes so that water can flow through them from the water point source. How you can accomplish this depends on the game mode. The game has a help section in the main menu where you can always check up on the rules of each game mode. The game has 375 levels, spread over 3 game mode each with 5 difficulties, so that is 25 levels per difficulty / game mode. To top that off the game also provides a random difficulty which will generate never ending, random levels for the game mode you had chosen.
    </p>
    <p>
      in Rotate Mode You need to connect all the pipes so water flows through them, by pressing the A button or X key on a pipe, to rotate the single pipe. In Slide Mode You need to connect all the pipes so water flows through them, by pressing the A button or X Key on the arrows of a row or column. The row or column will move all pipes in the direction the arrow is pointing at. In Roslid Mode You need to connect all the pipes so water flows through them, by pressing the A button or X key on the arrows of a row or column. The row or column will move all pipes in the direction the arrow is pointing at. You can also press the A button or X key on a pipe, to rotate the single pipe. This is a combination Rotate and Slide mode.
    </p>
  </description>
  
  <launchable type="desktop-id">io.github.joyrider3774.waternet_playdate.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joyrider3774/waternet_playdate/main/metadata/screenshots/Waternet-screenshot6.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joyrider3774/waternet_playdate/main/metadata/screenshots/Waternet-screenshot5.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joyrider3774/waternet_playdate/main/metadata/screenshots/Waternet-screenshot3.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
</component>